Finding Aid for the Michael Braver Collection of Americanist Material LSC.1585
UCLA Library Special Collections
Michael Braver collection of Americanist material
1960-1979
UCLA Library Special Collections
Braver, Michael
LSC.1585
12 Linear Feet (24 boxes, 1 oversize box)
Collection consists of over 300 speeches by Americanist right-wing extremist spokesmen on reel to reel and cassette tapes, as well as Americanist journals, books, pamphlets, booklets, and fugitive materials. Includes speakers from the John Birch Society, the National Socialist White Peoples' Party, Christian Crusade Convention, and the American Independent Party. Also includes literature from the Christian Anti-Communism Crusade, the Libertarian Party, the Minutemen, Sons of the American Revolution, and Voice of Americanism.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audiovisual materials. Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed audiovisual materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Michael Braver, 1989.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942304123606533
Biography
Michael Bruce Braver was born on Sept. 25, 1946 in New York City; AB, MA, UCLA, 1969; MSW, Univ. of Southern CA., 1978; Ph.D, CA School of Professional Psychology, 1983; became asst. professor, Central Washington Univ., 1969-71, winning a meritorious teaching award in 1969; clinical psychologist in private practice, Toluca Lake, CA, beginning in 1980.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of over 300 speeches by Americanist right-wing extremist spokesmen on reel to reel and cassette tapes, as well as Americanist journals, books, pamphlets, booklets, and fugitive materials. Includes speakers from the John Birch Society, the National Socialist White Peoples' Party, Christian Crusade Convention, and the American Independent Party. Also includes literature from the Christian Anti-Communism Crusade, the Libertarian Party, the Minutemen, Sons of the American Revolution, and Voice of Americanism.
Sound recordings.; Alternative publications.; Psychology teachers -- United States.; Clinical psychologists -- California, Southern.; Braver, Michael--Archives.
- Major Journals and Newsletters
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade (CACC) Newsletter. Selections, 1971-1975; 53 issues. (Box 17)
  - Christian Crusade (Annual), 1973, 1974; 2 issues. (Box 21)
  - Christian Crusade Weekly., 1973-1974.; 51 issues. (Box 22)
    - Volume 13, 1973
      Scope and Contents note
      Weekly beginning with Issue 21, April 1, 1973 through Issue 52, November 4, 1973 (incorrectly printed as issue 51). This includes 32 consecutive weekly issues.
    - Volume 14., 1973-1974.
      Weekly beginning with Issue 1, November 18, 1973 April 21, 1974. (incorrectly printed as issue 51). This includes 23 consecutive weekly issues.
  - Christian Vanguard., 1973-1975.; 21 issues. (Box 18)
    Published by the New Christian Crusade Church. This is a news journal that focuses on racial-religious issues in Americanist context.
  - Freedom., 1973-1974.; 3 issues. (Box 21)
    Summer 1973
    Spring 1974
    Summer 1974
  - The Independent American., 1973-1974.; 6 issues. (Box 21)
    Volume 19, Issues 1-6. Monthly Newspaper, Littleton, CO. "A National Conservative Newspaper founded in 1955."
  - John Birch Society Bulletin., 1973-1974.; 17 issues. (Box 16, 19)
  - Liberty Letter., 1972-1975.; 25 issues. (Box 16, 19, 21)
  - Dr. McBirnie's Newsletter., 1973-1975.; 27 issues. (Box 15, 19)
    Americanist Newsletter by a prominent Minister.
  - National Chronicle., 1973-1975.; 73 issues. (Box 18)
    Volume 22, 1973
    Volume 23, 1974
    Volume 24, 1975
  - Report on Freedom., 1969, 1973-1975.; 5 issues. (Box 21)
  - Review of the News (Anti-Communist Journal)., 1971-1972.; 15 issues. (Box 16)
  - The Utah Independent, 1972-1974; 37 issues. (Box 17)
    An Americanism-Oriented Newspaper. Issues from Volumes 3, 4 5.
  - Reprints from Review of the News and associated Birch Society pamphlets, 33 reprints and pamphlets.
    - Allen, Gary. "Fedcop." American Opinion., December 1970 (Box 19)
    - Allen, Gary. The Press. How the Left Turned Me Right. American Opinion., undated. (Box 19)
    - Anderson, Tom. For Christians. American Opinion., 1972 (Box 19)
    - American Opinion Bookstores Book List. (Box 19)
    - Benson, Ezra Taft. Stand Up for Freedom. American Opinion., 1966 (Box 19)
    - Blumenfeld, Samuel. About De Gaulle. American Opinion., 1962 (Box 19)
    - "Cross Section of the Truth" (no author), 1968 (Box 19)
    - Dennis, Delmar. The Will and the Way to Win. JBS., 1973 (Box 19)
    - Dunham, William. Communists Control the U.N. Review of the News., October 27, 1971. (Box 19)
    - Dunham, William. Potential Genocide. Review of the News., June 14, 1972. (Box 19)
    - Fenton, Fr. Francis. "Deceiving Catholics" Review of the News., November 1, 1972. (Box 19)
    - Griffin, Edward. The Grand Design. Thousand Oaks, CA: American Media., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Griffin. More Deadly than War. Thousand Oaks, CA: American Media., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Hayes, Lee. Remember the Pueblo. American Opinion., Undated. (Box 19)
    - McManus, John F. An Overview of Our World. John Birch Society., 1971. (Box 19)
    - "Movement to Restore Decency." (Motorede) (Box 19)
    - "Responsible Leadership Through the John Birch Society." (Box 19)
    - Schmitz, (Hon.) John. "Nixon's Red trade Helps Communists." Review., August 30, 1972. (Box 19)
    - Schuyler, George. Saint Martin? American Opinion., Undated. (Box 19)
    - Stang, A. "Oshacrats." American Opinion. (Box 19)
    - Welch, Robert. About Money and Other Matters., June 1, 1973. (Box 19)
    - Welch, Robert. If I Were President. John Birch Society., Undated.; (2 copies) (Box 19)
    - Welch. In One Lifetime. American Opinion., 1971. (Box 19)
    - Welch. More Stately Mansions. American Opinion., 1964. (Box 19)
    - Welch. More Truth About Vietnam. American Opinion., 1967. (Box 19)
    - Welch. "Republics and Democracies." American Opinion., October 1971; (2 copies) (Box 19)
    - Welch. The Truth about Vietnam. American Opinion., 1967. (Box 19)
    - Welch. The Truth in Time. American Opinion., November 1966. (Box 19)
    - Welch. "Through All the Days to Be" American Opinion., June 1961.; (2 copies) (Box 19)
    - Welch. "Two Revolutions at Once." American Opinion. (Box 19)
    - Welch. What is the John Birch Society. American Opinion. Reprint., 1970.; (2 copies) (Box 19)
    - Welch. "Why Join the John Birch Society." American Opinion., 1968.; (2 copies) (Box 19)
    - "Why People Become Communists." American Opinion., October 1958. (Box 19)
  - Booklets by Dr. Wesley A. Swift., 21 booklets.
    Many are transcriptions of sermons delivered to the Church of Jesus Christ, Christian in Hollywood, CA. Dr. Swift's sermons are concerned with America, Christianity, and Race. His publisher is the new Christian Crusade Church, P.O. Box 3247, Hollywood, CA 90028 which also publishes The Christian Vanguard, a newspaper of newsletter also concerned with America, Christianity, and Race. In some of the booklets, there is a disclaimer saying that Dr. Swift's Church is not necessarily in complete agreement with the New Christian Crusade Church.
    - Were All the People Drowned (Box 19)
    - Reopening the Trial of Jesus Christ (Box 19)
    - Give Not that which is Holy unto the Dogs (Box 19)
    - You, Before the World was Framed (Box 19)
    - The Sword of Truth, (2 copies) (Box 19)
    - The Blue Tunic Army of Christ (Box 19)
    - The Power of his Resurrection (Box 19)
    - Behold I Make All Things New (Box 19)
    - God, Man, Nations, and the Races (Box 19)
    - Who Crucified Jesus Christ (Box 19)
    - Hossanna in the Highest (Box 19)
    - Not Guilty (Box 19)
    - The Family of God (Box 19)
    - The Day God was Born (Box 19)
    - Heraldry of the Nations (Box 19)
    - Standards of the Kingdom (Box 19)
    - The Mystery of the Iniquity (Box 19)
    - In the Beginning (Box 19)
    - God's Call to Race (Box 19)
    - The Appointed Place (Box 19)
- Assorted Fugitive Materials and Limited Issues of Magazines
  Includes announcements, pamphlets, bulletins, internal memos, and transcripts.
  - A.C.T. (Association of Concerned Taxpayers).
    - "Think About It.", Pamphlet. (2 copies). (Box 15)
    - "Your Money and Your Life: IRS", Folio poster with skull and crossbones. (Box 15)
  - America First. (Box 15)
    (A 12 page tabloid concerned with "dangers of Zionism," published by Liberty Lobby, and intended for use by the American Party). Undated, apparently 1972, and possibly intended for the November election.
  - American Intelligence Agency. (Box 15)
    Membership Certificate, Special Bulletin, HotLine Newsletter, 2 issues, undated, probably 1972 or 1973.
  - Americanism Educational League: Buena Park, California.
    - How To Create an Energy Crisis. (Pamphlet $1) (Box 15)
    - Lechner, John. "Our Constitution and Tomorrow's Freedom. Los Angeles., November 17, 1963. (Box 15)
    - [Reverend Edward W. Greenfield sermons] (Box 15)
      The Following Three Citations were delivered as sermons by the Reverend Edward W. Greenfield at the Church of Reflections, Buena Park, CA. These are mimeod.
      - Greenfield, E. "These Dishonored Dead.", May 31, 1964. (Box 15)
      - Greenfield, E. "The Enemies We Resist.", October 11, 1964. (Box 15)
      - Greenfield, E. "The Heritage We Conserve.", October 4, 1964. (Box 15)
    - Benson, E.T. "Our Immediate Responsibility.", October 25, 1966. (Box 15)
      A classic Anti-Communist Speech.
  - American Media Publishers.
    - Spring Catalog for The Spoken Word Library., 1973. (Box 15)
    - Subscription form for the Spoken Word Series. (Box 15)
  - American Opinion Bookstore Booknews., April 1974. (Box 15)
  - American Opinion. Volume 15, #7. Scoreboard 1972 Issue., July-August 1972. (Box 15)
  - American's for Constitutional Action.
    - Moreell, Adm. Ben. "I'm Fed Up to Here." Washington, D.C., January 11, 1963. (Box 15)
  - Anti-Communist Book club Announcement of the Campus Conservative Pack program. (Box 15)
  - Ayn Rand Letter, The., 1972.
    - Volume II, No. 1., October 9, 1972. (Box 15)
    - Volume II, No. 2., October 23, 1972. (Box 15)
    - Volume II, No. 3., November 6, 1972. (Box 15)
  - Biggert, John W. Co., Undated.; 3 tracts and a newsletter. (Box 15)
  - Caxton Books Publications, 1972; 5 items. (Box 15)
    Announcements featuring Jo Hindman's three books: Terrible 1313 Revisited; Blame Metro; and The Metrocrats. Also a Chart of the Metro Conspiracy dated June 1972.
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade
    - CACC Bulletin/Newsletter., April 1, 1974. (Box 15)
    - CACC Bulletin/Newsletter., April 1, 1975. (Box 15)
    - Southern California Anti-Subversive Seminar Pamphlet., November 28-30, 1975. (Box 15)
    - Northern California Anti-Subversive Seminar Pamphlet., February 17-19, 1973. (Box 15)
    - U.S. Government Publications
      - Testimony of Dr. Frederick C. Schwarz. "Terroristic Activity." (Box 15)
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee to Investigate the Administration of the Internal Security Act of the Committee on the Judiciary, United States Senate. 93rd Congress, second session, Part 3., July 5, 1974. (Box 15)
  - Pamphlet. What Can I Do to Combat Communism. (Box 15)
  - Pamphlet. Insurance Against Communism. (Box 15)
  - Christian Crusade.
    - Fact File: Billy James Hargis., July 1971; (2 pages) (Box 15)
    - Fact File: David Noebel., July 1971; (1 page) (Box 15)
    - Fact File: Jess Pedigo., July 10, 1971; (1 page) (Box 15)
    - Hargis, B.J. Billy James Hargis Speaks Out On the Issues., 1971.; (31 pages) (Box 15)
    - History of the Christian Crusade., (3 pages) (Box 15)
    - Listing of Tapes for Sale from 1972 Conventions., (2 pages) (Box 15)
  - Christian Freedom Foundation, Inc. and Moral Advance.
    - Applied Christianity. Volume 2, Issue 2., February 1973. (Box 15)
    - Applied Christianity. Volume 2, Issue 3., March 1973. (Box 15)
    - For Real. Tabloid. Volume 3, Number 4., April 1973. (Box 15)
    - Kershner, Howard E. "The Hangman's Rope.", June 1, 1964.; (Pamphlet). (Box 15)
    - Moral Advance. Pamphlet about the organization. (Box 15)
    - Moral Advance Action News. Volume II, Number 4., April 1973. (Box 15)
    - Moral Advance Action News., Undated. (Box 15)
  - C.O.F.F.E.E. Community Organization for Full Employment Economy, Inc.
    - Parts of Articles of Incorporation, 1968, 1973.; 2 pages, mimeo. (Box 15)
  - Committee To Restore the Constitution.
    - Bulletin., November 1972. (Box 15)
    - Bulletin., August 1972. (Box 15)
  - FACTS Newsletter, Volume 1, Number 1. (Edited by Charles Wolff)., October 1971. (Box 15)
  - Family Heritage Series. Volume 1, Issue 20., August 1973. (Box 15)
  - FiPo (Fire and Police Research Association of Los Angeles)., Mimeo, 6 pages. (Box 15)
    Address by: Moore, Norman H. "The Trend to Render Law Enforcement Ineffective."
  - Freedom University. Announcement of Courses. (Box 15)
  - Free Enterprise Speakers Bureau. Xerox announcement of speakers., 19 pages. (Box 15)
  - Freemen Report. Volume 1, Number 15., March 30, 1973. (Box 15)
  - Gary Allen Communications. (Box 15)
    Assorted Announcements of Lectures, Autograph Parties. Tapes, Home Study Materials, etc. Gary Allen is the author of None Dare Call It Conspiracy, an important book among Birch Society Literature. (12 pages of assorted items and announcements, etc.)
  - H.O.W. (Happiness of Womanhood). "A Message of Great Urgency from Your President.", Undated, probably April 1972.; Printed. (Box 15)
  - Homefront. Newsletter of Institute for American Democracy. Volume 6, Number 5., May 1972. (Box 15)
  - Homemakers Guild of America. Watts, Robert B. "Highlights of Truth." La Jolla, CA., October 24, 1965. (Box 15)
  - How Much Government Do We Need. Announcement of a 3 week film series. (Box 15)
  - Jewish Statement of Americanists. Statement of Principles., February - March, 1967.; Mimeo. (Box 15)
    Originally printed in The Sandtown Story.
  - John Birch Society.
    - American Opinion Bookstore Introductory Letter. (Box 15)
    - "Are Guns to Blame?" Speech by Charles Smith. Burbank, CA., November 20, 1973. (Box 15)
    - Application for Membership. (Box 15)
    - Arthur Bremer Story, Announcement and return tear-off for film series. (Box 15)
    - Arthur Bremer Story, Announcement and pamphlet with advertising space. (Box 15)
    - Beliefs and Principles of the John Birch Society. (Box 15)
      Extension of Remarks of the Hon. John H. Rousselot of CA in the House of Representatives, June 12, 1962. Congressional Record, 87th Congress, second session.
    - Call Him Correct. Reprint from a Mike Culbert Article. JBS., August 26, 1971. (Box 15)
    - China. Talk by Richard Chien. Sponsored by TRAIN Committee. Grenada Hills, CA., January (Box 15)
    - Continuing Support Club Contribution Form. (Box 15)
    - Currently Most in Demand Books and Reprints from American Opinion, October 1972. (Box 15)
    - Currently Most in Demand Books and Reprints from American Opinion, Spring 1973 (Box 15)
    - Dues Schedule for the John Birch Society (Box 15)
    - Elliot Graham campaign poster announcement. (Box 15)
    - Fenton, Rev. F. The John Birch Society. Speech Announcement, October 26, 1971 (Box 15)
    - "Foreign Policy and Domestic Policies." Announcing film series., February 28, 1973. (Box 15)
    - Half a Dozen Searchlights. Western Islands Publishing. (Box 15)
    - How Long Will You Stand Aside., (4 pages). (Box 15)
    - If There Were No United Nations., Pamphlet. (Box 15)
    - James Toevs Schedule 1973: Speaking on the Ecology Hysteria. (Box 15)
    - JBS Confronts the Issues of 1972., Xeroxed Announcement. (Box 15)
    - John Birch Society Local Chapters Sponsor Tim Heinan Speaking on "The Arthur Bremer Story" (attempted assassin of George Wallace)., Announcement, 1 page. (Box 15)
    - Members Monthly Message Form (Box 15)
    - Outline of Basic Principles and Beliefs, (2 sides, printed). (Box 15)
    - Protest Check against monetary settlement with North Vietnam. (Box 15)
    - Protest to the President., 1972.; 4 pages. (Box 15)
    - Six Best Sellers for the Price of Three. (Box 15)
      American Opinion Bookstore Announcement.
    - Visit to the John Birch Society. Announcement of TV program for a local Independent Station, January 10, 1973. (Box 15)
    - We Can Stop America's Retreat from Greatness. Tabloid Reprint., 1971. (Box 15)
    - What's Wrong with Civil Rights?, (2 pages pamphlet). (Box 15)
    - Why Warren Should be Impeached. Flyer. (Box 15)
  - Keech Lottye Kilgo. Is there a Difference between a Khazar Jew and a Palestinian Jew?, 16 pages. (Box 15)
    Published by Militant for Christ. P.O. Box 22, Twin Peaks, CA 92391.
  - Key Records. The Big 5 Anti-Communist Record Albums., undated. (Box 15)
  - Legislative Research Associates, Inc. "It is Unbelievable; The Story of Money.", undated.; Pamphlet. (Box 15)
  - Libertarian Party.
    - 1972 Platform. (Box 15)
    - 1974 Platform (Box 15)
    - Hospers, John. (U.S. Pres. Nominee of Libertarian Party). Restoring Liberty to America. Los Angeles (?), July 4, 1972. (Box 15)
    - Reason. Intro Pamphlet for Reason Magazine. (Box 15)
    - Taxation is Theft. Publication of Society for Individual Liberty and Distributed by the Libertarian Party., (1972); (Pamphlet) (Box 15)
    - Tired of Being the Politicians' Puppet?, (1972).; (Libertarian Pamphlet). (Box 15)
  - Liberty Lobby
    - Liberty Lobby Progress Report, 1974 (Annual) (Box 15)
    - Emergency Liberty Letter #31, "Genocide Treaty Trap.", May 14, 1973. (Box 15)
    - "Un-Tax Me.", Pamphlet. (Box 15)
    - Liberty Lowdown #106., January 1972; (2 pages). (Box 15)
    - Who's Your Lobbyist in Washington; The Story of Liberty Lobby, (Pamphlet) (Box 15)
  - "Mayday at May Co." Announcement of Protest of Peace Booth at May Company., 1970. (Box 15)
  - Minutemen, The.
    - Kershner, Howard. The Communist Takeover of America. San Diego., April 17, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Speech Reprinted by The Minutemen., 6 pages. (Box 15)
  - National Educator (special tax issue)., October-November 1972. (Box 15)
  - National Educator (volume 4, number 11)., April 1973 (Box 15)
  - National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation, Inc.
    - Pamphlet of Introduction. (Box 15)
    - "Cesar Chavez--Harvest of Tyranny." Reprint from Kilpatrick, J. The Evening Star, Washington D.C., July 14, 1970. (Box 15)
  - National Socialist White Peoples Party:
    - Back to Africa Boat Ticket., (1972). (Box 15)
    - Battle Song of the NSWPP. (Box 15)
    - Exposing the Haters. Reprint of an Article by M. Kahane about NSWPP (Box 15)
    - Letter of Information/Introduction. (Box 15)
    - Official Supporter Application Form (Box 15)
    - What is National Socialist White Peoples Party?, Printed, 1 page, 2 sides (Box 15)
    - White Power (Newspaper), August 1972 and February 1973.; (2 issues). (Box 15)
    - Western States Combat Report, November 1972-January 1973.; (Printed). (Box 15)
  - Network, The (of Patriotic Letter Writers). "Important Letters.", January 1973. (Box 15)
  - New Christian Crusade Church. (Box 15)
    Letters from James K. Warner enclosed with Christian Vanguard and otherwise available. 7 letter dated March 1973; April 1973; June 1973; July 1973; August-September 1973; October 1973; October 9, 1973; December 1973.
  - New England Rally for God, Family, and Country.
    Held Annually in Boston, MA.
    - Benson, Ezra T. "Strength for the Battle.", July 4, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Fenton, Rev. Francis. "Morality and Decency are Under Attack.", July 6, 1969. (Box 15)
    - Fenton, Rev. Francis. "The Treason of the Churches.", 1972. (Box 15)
  - No Aid to Hanoi., (3 pages). (Box 15)
    Announcement of program, appeal to write protest.
  - Objectivist Book Service, Inc. Reading List. (Box 15)
  - Patriotic Program Log (Coast Federal Savings)., undated.; 2 pages. xerox. (Box 15)
  - P.A.T. (Parents and Taxpayers).
    - Reprint from S.F. Examiner on a "Tax Martyr", February 25, 1973.; (2 copies). (Box 15)
    - Reprint from Phoenix Gazette re Billy Graham on Debts, March 11, 1969. (Box 15)
  - Paxton, Floyd. "Who's Whose in America." Paid Advertisement, Yakima Herald Republic, April 3, 1973. (Box 15)
  - Poor Richard's Bookshop. Letter and some recommendations for reading. (Box 15)
  - Radio Verite.
    - (Ron Wright). Announcement and Statement of Beliefs. (Box 15)
    - Broadcast #254. Jam the Computers., March 23, 1973. (Box 15)
    - Broadcast #257 Should Big Brother Take Vitamins., April 13, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Report on Freedom Volume 8, Issue 4, December 1973 (Box 15)
  - Sons of the American Revolution
    - S.A.R. Magazine, Vol. LXVII, No. 2, Fall 1972. (Box 15)
    - Dilworth, Nelson. "Can America Maintain Peace?" (Box 15)
      Address to Kiwanis Club of San Diego as guests of the San Diego Chapter of California Society of the Sons of the American Revolution, later published by the Senate of the California Legislature. August 25, 1959.
  - Sons of Liberty Books for Patriots, 1974 (Annual) (Box 15)
  - "Stop Immorality on TV." Statement of purposes, appeal for support., 6 pages. (Box 15)
  - Support Your Local Police., 5 pages. (Box 15)
  - Tax Fax #131 What's Behind the Watergate Scandal. (Box 15)
  - Tax Rebellion Committee. "The Global Concept." #159., January 31, 1973.; 8 pages. (Box 15)
  - Tax Strike Digest., Summer 1972 (Box 15)
    (12 page tabloid, excerpts from American Mercury)
  - Tax Strike News. (Box 15)
    Volume 4, No. 1, January 1973.
    Volume 4, No. 2, February 1973.
    Volume 4, No. 3, March 1973.
    Volume 4, No. 4, April 1973.
  - T.A.C.T. (Truth About Civil Turmoil).
    - Charles Smith, 1 page. (Box 15)
    - "Poverty Warriors" (Box 15)
      Reprint from Barrons. "The Riots are Subsidized.
    - "America Blackmailed." (Box 15)
      A Reprint from Babson's Letter.
    - Patriotic Preview. (Box 15)
      A list of speeches and films.
  - T.R.A.I.N. To Restore American Independence Now., 8 pages. (Box 15)
  - TRUE (Tax Reformers United Endeavor)., 20 pages. (Box 15)
  - TRUE NEWS Volume 1, Ed. 3. Special Bi-Centennial Tea Party Issue, 1972-1973.; (3 copies). (Box 15)
    - California Mining Journal, Vol 42, #6, February 1973.; (2 pages, anti-IRS) (Box 15)
    - "Don't Miss the Boat" Announcement of "Liberty Tea", April 15, 1973. (Box 15)
    - "Liberty Tea" Souvenir Song Sheet, April 15, 1973. (Box 15)
  - U.S.A. (United in Service to America)., 15 Items. (Box 15)
  - Voice of Americanism., Radio Log, Newspaper, Poster, Announcement, and 10 Pamphlets. (Box 15)
    The pamphlets are as follows:
    The Plot to Destroy Anti-Communism in America What is Ahead for America Now?
    How George McGovern Intends to Radicalize America The Real Story of the Pilgrims
    How the Communists Plan Race War
    Why are the Fires of Inflation Mounting?
    Forked Tongues at Wounded Knee ("Subversion and Sedition")
    Why We Should Not Trade with our Deadly Enemy
    Six Perils of Coexistence.
    What You Should Be in '73.
  - Washington Observer Newsletter #157, April 15, 1973. (Box 15)
  - We the People., A Mimeo'd Newsletter. Usually 2 to 6 pages. 8 issues. (Box 15)
    Volume 1, Issue 35: March 5, 1973
    Volume 1, Issue 36: March 12, 1973
    Volume 1, Issue 40: April 9, 1973
    Volume 1, Issue 42: April 27, 1972
    Volume 1, Issue 43: April 30, 1973